原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我叫卡拉·佐·艾尔
My name is Kara Zor-El.
我来自氪星
I'm from Krypton.
我来到这颗星球避难
I'm a refugee on this planet.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我被派往地球保护我的堂弟
I was sent to Earth to protect my cousin.
但我的太空舱被击中后偏离路线
But my pod got knocked off course.
在我到达地球之时
And by the time I got here,
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我的堂弟已经长大  成为了超人
my cousin had already grown up and become... Superman.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我隐藏了我的真实身份
I hid who I really was
直到最近的一起事故
until one day when an accident
迫使我向世界揭示了自己的身份
forced me to reveal myself to the world.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
对于大多数人  包括我收养家庭的姐姐艾丽克斯
To most people, including my adoptive sister Alex,
后期     你是不是饿得慌
我只是凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
I'm a reporter at CatCo Worldwide Media.
但私下里  我保护着这颗我称之为家园的星球
But in secret, I work to protect this planet I call my home
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不受任何人的伤害
from anyone that means to cause it harm.
我是超女
I am Supergirl.
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
我是来跟你签订一份政府合同的
I'm here to offer you a government contract.
我们需要让美国军队
We need to make the US military
与我们的外星对手一样强大
as powerful as our alien adversaries.
我从来没有打算同意你
I am never going to agree with you
去和政府分享你的研究
sharing your research with the government.
-我觉得你该走了  -所以就这样吗
- I think you should leave. - So, that's it then.
你的超能力让你有
Your powers give you the potential
成为伟大英雄的潜力
to be a great hero.
但你仍然需要学习控制超能力
But you still have to learn how to control them.
我需要你帮我训练
What I need is for you to help me train.
军团万岁
Long live the Legion!
给你的信
Letter for you.
-谁寄的  -曼彻斯特·布莱克
- From who? - Manchester Black.
《爱国者法案》只保护人类生命
The Patriot Act only protects human life.
洛克伍德不能被起诉
Lockwood can't be charged under it.
让白宫法律顾问马上签字
Get the White House Counsel to sign off, now.
我在此  作为一个自由的人
I stand before you a free man,
准备继续服务于这个伟大的国家
ready to continue to serve this great nation.
感谢
Cheers!
你在监狱工作
You work in the prison.
-你的名字叫丹尼  -你说什么
- Your name's Danny. - What did you say?
你喜欢惊喜吗  丹尼
Do you like surprises, Danny?
不要  住手
No, wait!
超 女
第四季 第十三集
刚从打印机里出来的
Hot off the laser jet.
让我猜猜  这是在洛克伍德出狱后
Let me guess, this is your sixth article
你写的第六篇关于他的文章
on Lockwood since he got out of prison?
-新角度吗  -不是
- New angle? - Nope.
但是人们需要时刻被提醒着
But people need to be reminded, you know,
他是个杀人凶手
that... that he's a murderer.
是这样没错
There's that.
感觉我是在对空呼喊  但是...
Feels like I'm screaming into the void, but...
你想要把空喊留到我们吃饭之后吗
You wanna save that void screaming until after we eat?
詹姆斯
James.
午餐  我的天啊  午餐  我完全忘了
Lunch... Oh, my God, lunch. I totally forgot.
-坏坏  卡拉太坏了  -别这样  太丢人了
- Bad! Kara is so bad-- - Okay, you're embarrassing.
咱们走吧
Let's go.
我们还去外出取材吗
Are we still on for the, um, research trip?
最近因为洛克伍德的事太忙了
Things have been so busy with all the Lockwood stuff
我完全忘了和市审计员
that I totally forgot we have an appointment
有过约定
with the city auditor.
-真对不起  -没事
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
你也不过是个凡人
You're only human.
我等下给你打电话
Uh, I'll call you later.
好
Okay.
我想我也该走了  我...
Well, I guess I'll get a move on, too. I...
工作真是太忙了
Work has been crazy
莉娜这周要进驻超查部  简直...
with Lena moving into the DEO this week. It's...
-真对不起  -没事  我...
- That was... I'm sorry. - It's fine. I...
不需要这么小心翼翼的  谢了
No kid gloves needed. Thanks.
好吧  那我们改天再见
Okay, I'll see you soon?
但愿如此
I hope so.
这个来自我纳欣诺大学的一个朋友
This came from a friend at NCU
他几个月前申请了一项
who applied for like a medical study
医学研究
a few months ago.
他没有被选中  但是...
He didn't get picked up, but...
那个地址属于L公司的一家子公司
That address is to an L-Corp subsidiary.
我知道你说过
I know you said that my source
我上一篇文章的来源有误  但是
for that last article was wrong, but
你觉得值得再调查一下吗
you think it's worth taking a second look?
打着外出的幌子去训练  我这谎撒得怎么样
Did I cover okay about training and everything?
-我露馅了吗  -没有  没有
- Did I blow it? - No, no!
我也在适应对艾丽克斯撒谎呢
I'm still getting used to the lying to Alex, too.
别担心了
And don't worry,
你会对偷跑出去这种事越来越熟悉的
you'll get better at the whole "sneaking out" thing.
关键在于轻描淡写
The key is subtlety.
例子来了
Case in point.
你好  布莱尼
Hi, Brainy.
是巴尼
It's Barney.
-巴尼  -是的  巴尼
- Barney? - Yes, Barney.
我想着最好低调一点
Thought it best we keep a low profile,
考虑到我们要去的地方
considering where we're going.
欢迎来到孤独堡垒
Welcome to the Fortress of Solitude.
反正是比你那小公寓好多了
I mean, it sure beats the hell out of your loft.
那地方是受租金管制的
Hey! That place is rent-controlled.
这里用来训练非常好
And this works great for training.
再说  你还有凯里克斯
Plus, you have Kelex, too.
我不知道咱们要接待客人
I did not know we would be receiving guests.
你还有个机器人
You have a robot?
机器人管家马克五号
Caretaker Android Mark IV
有着多样功能
with many other functions.
凯里克斯  这是尼娅·纳尔
Kelex, this is Nia Nal.
满足她的一切需求
Give her anything she needs.
我想露易丝已经向你介绍过
And I think Lois already introduced you
布莱尼了  对吗
to Brainy, right?
-你好  凯林尼克斯  -是凯里克斯  奎罗尔
- Hello, Kleenex. -It's Kelex, Querl.
你不需要去打扫宇宙铁砧什么的吗
Don't you have to dust the cosmic anvil or something?
好吧  有什么需要就喊我
Okay... Holler if you need me.
已经好几周了
It's been weeks.
现在你同意见我了
And now you agree to see me?
为什么是现在
Why now?
就当是
Well, let's just say
监狱改变了我吧
prison has changed me.
说实话
So, be honest...
你觉得这发型如何
Whatcha think of the hair?
你失去了某人
Look, you lost someone.
我知道那是什么感受
I know how that feels.
让我帮助你
Let me help you.
你觉得我内心深处是个好人吧
You think I'm good deep down, eh?
现在这时代做好人可行不通
Well, it's a bad time to be a good man.
就拿你来说
Take you, for instance.
如果不是因为你的誓言
If it weren't for your bloody promise,
我想你可以解决世界上所有的问题
I believe you could solve all the worlds problems.
你只是需要  动机
You just need... motivation.
这是帽子  我们是老交情了
This is Hat. We go way back.
好呀
'Ello!
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
我想当面谢谢你
I wanted to thank you in person.
我之前眼光太狭隘了
I was thinking small.
一心想干掉洛克伍德复仇
Hell-bent on getting Lockwood. Petty revenge.
但我有更大的鱼要杀
But I've got bigger fish to murder.
你阻止不了我的  老人家
And you can't stop me, old man.
别这样做
Don't do this.
多谢你来陪我聊天  伙计
Thanks for the chat, mate.
让我精神多了
Cheered me right up.
我这就把咱们传送出去吗
Shall I teleport us out, then?
还不行  还得再去一个地方
Ah, not yet. Gotta make another stop.
我只能送我们去我以前去过的地方
I can't take us anywhere I haven't been before.
眼下只能来硬的了
We'll have to do it the hard way.
这对我们来说从来都不是问题
When's that ever stopped us?
你没枪了吗
All out of guns?
我以为你会喜欢带劲一点的武器
Thought you'd like something dashing.
不许动  趴下
Freeze! Down on the ground!
调皮
Naughty.
是什么如此重要
So, what's important enough for you
让你拿我们的刺激大逃亡冒险
to jeopardize our thrilling escape?
就一件破外套  为什么
A bloody jacket! Why?
带劲啊
It's dashing.
好久不见
Long time no see.
这发条橙是谁
Who's Clockwork Orange?
那句话是怎么说的来着  "有朋友的人"
What's the line? "No man is a failure --"
"都不算失败"
"...who has friends."
你不是被我们抓住了吗
I thought we captured you.
她说那是另一个莫拉人
She says that was a different Morae.
在你眼里都长得一样
They all look alike to you.
你来了
There you are.
很高兴终于见到你了
Nice to finally meet you.
梅纳热里
Menagerie?
你以为砍掉蛇头就能消灭我们
Thought you could cut off the head of the snake.
我们没那么软弱
We're tougher than that.
-放开他  -为什么  这是战争
- Let him go. - Why would we? It's war.
你知道那些憎恨外星人的种族主义者
You know those alien-hating racists
都纷纷从洞里冒出头了吗
been comin' out their hidey holes?
我们要弄死他们
We're gonna make them dead.
那好
Right then...
曼彻斯特
Manchester!
我会把他们找出来
I'm gonna find them.
我也一起去
Not without me.
你有预知的梦境
You have anticipatory dreams,
我有微分学
I have differential calculus.
两者都有预测性
Both are predictive,
但是
but...
我们也必须随机应变
We have to be adaptive, too.
这是我从我朋友瓦尔那学到的
I learned that from my friend Val.
你的军团朋友之一吗
One of your Legion friends?
他的事你就可以告诉我
So him I'm allowed to know about?
布莱尼  你认识我在未来的后裔之一
Brainy, you knew one of my descendants in the future,
可你却不告诉我关于她的任何事
but you won't tell me a thing about her.
可假如我能全面了解她的能力
But if I knew the full scope of what she could do --
绝对不行
Absolutely not!
我们可能引发悖论
Yeah, we could create a paradox,
-毁掉时空的  -时空的结构
- destroy the very fabric -- - Fabric of space-time.
你都说过无数次了
Where have I heard that before?
怎么了
What is it?
出什么事了
What's wrong?
把画面调出来
Pull up the footage.
这是直播  在里约
This is live. Rio.
我们想发送一条信息
We want to send a message.
居然仰拍  你疯了吗
Low angle? Are you insane?
什么
What?
我们正在某秘密军事基地进行直播
We are live from a secret army base
这里的雇佣兵无聊时就折磨外星人
where mercenaries torture aliens when they get bored.
他们杀害了我们四个同胞
They killed four of ours,
所以我们杀了他们一个  两个
so we killed one, two...
十三个人
Thirteen of theirs.
从现在起
From now on,
我们以极端偏见终结偏见
we terminate prejudice with extreme prejudice.
点个赞并订阅哦
Like and subscribe!
我会追踪到他们
I'll track them.
氪星科技远先进于地球科技
Kryptonian technology is far superior to Earth's.
当然  凯里克斯刨除在外
With, of course, the clear exception of Kelex.
我见过那种帽子
I've seen hats like that before.
用的是五维能量
They use Fifth Dimensional energy.
无法追踪
Untraceable.
我们在尽力追捕  可他们实在动作太快
We're trying to keep up, but they are just moving so fast.
居然败给了一顶帽子
Outmatched by a freaking hat.
我去和联合主席们谈谈
I'll talk to the Joint Chiefs,
看他们准不准我们出国
see if they want us overseas.
交给我来谈
I'll handle that.
我还得确定卢瑟女士的实验进展顺利
I need to also make sure Ms. Luthor is settled in.
-这个可以交给我  -好
- I can take that off your plate. - Okay.
凝胶电泳装置在哪
Where's the gel electrophoresis apparatus?
在那个房间  右边数第三个柜子
That would be in that room, third cabinet on the right.
这过去是我的实验室
Well, this used to be my lab.
交给你我很放心
I'm glad it's in good hands.
不过几周而已
It's just for a couple of weeks.
除非你想脱掉战服穿上白大褂
Unless you wanna change that combat suit for a white coat?
我能看看吗
May I?
好的
Okay...
这么说你正在
So, you are...
减少线粒体自噬
reducing mitophagy and...
同时增加线粒体效率
increasing mitochondrial efficiency at the same time.
这能让肌肉细胞拥有潜力去
That would give muscle cells the potential to...
等等
Okay, wait.
感恩节时你跟我说的那件事
That conversation at Thanksgiving,
不只是理论上的吗
that wasn't theoretical?
你在赋予人类超能力
You're giving people powers.
你的天资做管理层太浪费了
Management is such a waste of your talents.
莉娜  这非同小可
Lena, this is huge.
还很危险
And it's dangerous.
我们得加强你的保全
I mean, we need to up your security.
我们得确保
We need to make sure that
你的报告上传到受保护的服务器
your reports are put on a protected server.
我不会写任何报告的
I'm not going to be writing any reports.
不写报告是什么意思
What do you mean, you're not?
你与政府达成了协议
You made a deal with the government.
那协议是单向的
The deal was nonreciprocal.
只包括成品  不包括程序
It's for products, not procedures.
这样很好  因为我通常不信任政府
Which is a good thing, because I don't trust governments as a rule.
我就是政府
I'm the government.
我真希望事实不是这样
Well, I sure hope that's not true.
艾丽克斯  这不是私人恩怨
Alex, it's not personal.
我保证
I promise.
本·洛克伍德
Ben Lockwood?
欢迎来到华盛顿
Welcome to D.C.
签名要写送给谁的
Yeah, who should I make it out to?
你一直躲着不接我电话那个人
The guy whose phone calls you been dodging.
抱歉  我误会了
I'm sorry, I didn't... realize.
没关系  我是库珀
It's all good. I'm Cooper,
为自由之子服务
serving the Children of Liberty
保卫我国首都及周边地区
in our nation's capital and areas surrounding.
好极了  谢谢
Right on. Thanks.
来杯三指深的威士忌
Jack. Three fingers.
我们一直呵护着自由之火  生生不息
We've been keeping Liberty's torch lit, so to speak.
还在打理组织事务  因为你当时...
You know, taking care of things while you were... Well, you know.
我是来跟你说  我一直跟兄弟们待在一起
Came to say, I'm on the ground with the boys.
他们并不喜欢你最近的做法
And they don't love your conduct of late.
我有好消息要跟兄弟们分享
Well, I got good news for the boys.
我很快就要跟美国总统见面了
I'm about to meet with the President of the United States.
曼彻斯特·布莱克要逍遥法外了
Manchester Black is running free,
你却要西装革履地去国会山庄吗
and you're here with the suits on Capitol Hill?
-等等  你说什么  -你不知道吗
- Wait. What? - You didn't know?
他越狱了
Yeah, he broke out.
这正是我想说的  教授
This is exactly my point, Professor.
这一切刚开始的时候
Okay, when this whole thing started,
你害怕极了
you were downright scary.
可是现在呢
And now?
我家里有条狗  麦克斯
I got a dog back home, Max.
狗很乖
Great dog.
我们给它做了绝育之后
The day we neutered him,
它再没发出过以前的叫声
he didn't bark the same no more.
好吧
Okay. Yeah.
没人会信服喝果汁的男人
Nobody is gonna follow this.
他的餐费算我账上
Put his on my tab.
曼彻斯特·布莱克和他的手下是什么
Who are Manchester Black and his cohorts?
有些人觉得  他们是恐怖分子
To some, they are terrorists.
其他人觉得  他们是正义之士
To others, they're a force for good,
对抗着全球的外星人差别待遇
fighting against alien discrimination worldwide.
每种行为都有正反面  对吗
Every action has an opposite and equal, yeah?
地球的首批"自由"群众
This Earth first "Liberty" crowd,
他们伤害了外星人
they hurt aliens.
怎么  他们觉得我们不会反击吗
And what, they don't think we'll hurt them in kind?
这个来自伦敦
That's London.
看来他们偷了御宝
And it looks like they stole the crown jewels
是想引起更大的关注
to make a bigger statement.
怎么  因为超女说不应该这样做吗
Why? 'Cause Supergirl says that's not the way?
超女就像民间故事
Supergirl's like a folktale.
理论上看  很高尚  令人安心
In theory, comforting, noble.
在现实中  不够完善
In reality, ill-equipped
而且执着于早已过时的理想
and clinging to ideals of a time long past.
他们往道德低点走  她往道德高点走
When they go low, she goes high.
我们会让他们下场更惨
We put them six feet lower.
我们受够了总让那些魔鬼钻法律的空子
We're through giving these devils the benefit of the law.
超女已经完了
Supergirl's done.
现在是精英的时代
This is the era of the Elite.
我斗胆猜想一下
Now, if I flatter myself,
我觉得"昨日之女"
my guess is the Girl of Yesterday
应该在哪里看着  两手叉腰
is watching somewhere, hands on her hips
打着正义的旗号
in the name of justice,
她也可以直接来见我
or she can come meet me face-to-face.
黎明时分  独自过来
Dawn. Come alone.
希望你能赶到
I hope you can make it.
这就是你一直主张的  对吗
That's what you're all about, right?
"希望"
"Hope"?
接下来是广告时间
Now, for a commercial break.
你不能信任他  肯定是圈套
You cannot trust him. It'll be a trap.
我走进圈套也不是第一次了
Wouldn't be the first one I've walked into.
他甚至没说见面地点在哪里
He didn't even say where to meet.
信息最后的闪光里
That flash at the end of the message
加了一张图片
had an image coded in it.
只有我能看到的地图
A map only I could see.
结构光中嵌入的超光速信号
Superliminal stimuli embedded in structured light.
我不想佩服他  但是...
I don't want to be impressed, but...
他想在哪里见面
Where does he want to meet?
英国  曼彻斯特
Manchester, England.
看来他想要主场优势
Guess he wanted home court advantage.
离黎明还有多久
How long till dawn?
3小时21分钟15秒
Three hours, 21 minutes, 15 seconds.
那我们等等  然后我来处理他们
So we wait. And then I'll deal with them.
1935年7月5日 《劳工关系法》
罗斯福的笔
Fdr's.
曾用来签署《劳工关系法》
Used it to sign the Labor Relations Act.
你爸原来是工会的  对吧
Your dad was a union man, right?
是的  长官  一直是
Oh, yes, sir. Through and through.
是吗  来吧
Yeah? Come on.
总统先生  既然我来了这里
Uh, Mr. President, while I'm here,
我是代表很多人来的
I speak for a lot of people,
很多好人
a lot of good people.
很多希望能为您效力的人
People who are interested in service.
-所以我在想  -效力
- And so, I was thinking-- - Service?
这是什么意思
What are you saying?
你知道我的人效率很高
Well, you know how effective my people can be.
如今这个世界里
And with the world where it is today,
外面有着精英的威胁
and with the Elite being out there...
我希望你授权自由之子为你所用
I want you to deputize the Children of Liberty.
什么
What?
我喜欢你的节目
I like your show, son,
我能够帮你取得特赦  也很开心
and I'm glad I could help you out with the pardon,
但是眼下的形势在我掌控之中
but I've got the situation pretty well in hand.
懂吗
All right?
你需要做的
All you gotta do
就是在镜头下笑得开心点
is look pretty for the cameras.
对了  西装不错
Nice suit, by the way.
我已经决定了
I've made up my mind.
你无法说服我改变主意
You can't convince me to change it.
我很了解你
I know you better than that.
只是别让他把你打垮
Just don't let him bring you down.
曼彻斯特干扰了你  对不对  在监狱里
Manchester got to you, didn't he? At the prison.
我父亲死后  我唯一想做的就是向他致敬
All I've wanted to do since my father died is honor him.
以他为榜样活着
Live by his example.
你做到了
And you have.
但我很痛苦  卡拉
But I'm struggling, Kara.
我的内心在猛烈地挣扎
There's a duality in me that's at war.
我想像我父亲一样做一个和平的人
I want to be a man of peace just like my father,
但我浑身上下都在反抗这一想法
but every fiber of my being is fighting against that.
做火星猎人是我的天性
Being a Manhunter was part of my nature.
你在考虑重新拿起那把剑吗
Are you considering picking back up the sword?
我发过誓  不会轻易食言
I made a personal vow I wouldn't take that lightly.
如果你选择加入战斗  将精英绳之以法
Well, if you choose to join the fight to bring the Elite to justice,
我相信你父亲一定会理解
I'm sure your father would understand.
连梅林都加入过抗击主宰的战争
Even Myr'nn joined the fight against Reign.
曼彻斯特在用饵钓我
Manchester is baiting me.
我们之间有某种连接
We're connected somehow.
我觉得他能感觉到我内心的盛怒
I think he can feel the rage that lies within me.
来自我的全家被屠杀的愤怒
The rage born of the massacre of my family.
有一件事可以肯定
One thing's for certain,
曼彻斯特对我来说是一次测试
Manchester was a test for me.
但他到底是来测试我的决心
But whether he's a test of my resolve,
还是让我看到
or just a mirror
我不能走父亲的那条路
showing me that I cannot walk my father's path,
我真的不知道
I just don't know.
你会想清楚的  荣恩
You will find clarity, J'onn.
我知道你一定可以
I know you will.
谢谢
Thank you.
你希望我跟你一起去吗
Do you want me to come with you?
我需要一个人去
I think I need to do this alone.
他找我宣战  一定是有原因的
There's a reason he brought the fight to me.
我是那个象征
I'm the symbol.
他要超女的命
He wants this.
凯里克斯
Kelex?
尼娅·纳尔  很高兴你没把无聊的奎罗尔带来
Nia Nal, it's nice to see you without that bore Querl.
这颗星已经灭亡
This star has died.
那里出现了一颗新星
And there, a new one emerges.
那么  你很懂这些东西
So, you know about this stuff.
其他星系
Other systems?
星球
Planets?
我没理解错的话  你是在暗示
If I'm interpreting your intimations correctly,
你要寻找关于你们人种的信息
you seek information on your species.
你不应该问你那傲慢的慧核星朋友吗
Shouldn't you ask your pompous Coluan friend?
布莱尼不想公开那些信息
Brainy wants to keep all that under wraps.
但我如果要战斗
But if I'm supposed to fight,
就应该知道自己的能力
I need to know what I'm capable of.
唯一能告诉我的人已经...  不在了
The only other person who could've told me is... gone.
你的时间线很可能是超洛伦兹型的
Your timeline is likely extra-Lorentzian,
并不如想象中那么容易产生悖论
and not as subject to paradox as one might think.
但泄露这类信息仍旧有风险
But there are still risks to divulging this type of information.
超女说我需要什么都可以提
Well, Supergirl said anything I need,
不是吗
didn't she?
那是她的命令
Those were her orders.
那就告诉我纳尔托尔的信息吧
Then tell me about Naltor.
告诉我我所能做到的一切
Tell me about everything I can do.
英国  曼彻斯特
你可以从门进来的
You could have just used the door.
而你可以停止杀人的
And you could stop killing people.
请吧  不过别耍花招
Please, but no tricks.
如果我出事了  莫拉就会开始屠杀
If anything happens to me, the Morae will start killing.
然后呢  我们就在这坐着
So, what? We're just gonna sit here
模仿《盗火线》里那个晚餐镜头吗
and do the diner scene from Heat?
不不不
Ah, no, no.
帕西诺  德妮罗也来了
Ah, Pacino, De Niro, they came alone.
他们是来保护我的
They're just for my protection.
对我来说有点多余
It's a little gaudy for me.
那是我的报酬
Hey, that's my fee.
你不是只想着要报自己的血海深仇吗
I thought you were all about your vendetta.
本·洛克伍德  菲奥纳
Ben Lockwood, Fiona.
你觉得我为什么来这里
Why do you think I came here?
把她的东西带给她家人
Brought her things to her family.
洛克伍德会受到应有的惩罚
Lockwood's time will come.
但这事关你我
But this is about me and you.
你不肯加入我们  我也打不败你
You won't join us, and I can't beat you.
那就做个交易吧
So, let's make a deal.
我接受你的投降
I accept your surrender.
我决不会投降  但我可以不插手你的事
Never. But I can stay out of your soup.
树上猫  紧身衣蠢货和银行劫匪  都交给你
Cat in a tree, idiot in tights, bank robbers, all yours.
但是种族主义者  法西斯主义者  自由之子
But the racists, the fascists, the Children of Liberty,
我们来管
that's our department.
我不会让你继续杀人
I won't let you keep killing people.
所以你们政府是准备杀人吗
Oh, like your government intends to kill people?
你是真不知道吧
You really don't know, do you?
下周  你敬爱的政府
Next week, your beloved government
要发射一颗卫星  用来击落
is launching a satellite that will shoot down
所有想进入地球大气的外星宇宙飞船
any alien spacecraft trying to enter our atmosphere.
不可能
That's impossible.
我保证信息可靠
I have it on good authority.
他绑架了秘密特工
Hat kidnaps secret agent types,
了解到他们在干什么
learns what they're up to.
所以我们才成立这好汉帮
That's why we formed this band of merry men.
不好意思  是好人帮
Sorry, merry people.
我为什么要相信你
Why should I believe you?
问你的好同伴贝克吧
Talk to your mate, Baker.
那家伙刚赦免了
You know, the bloke who just pardoned
十恶不赦的自由之子首领
the grand bloody wizard of the Children of Liberty.
问他克莱莫行动是什么
Ask him 'bout Operation Claymore.
然后问问你自己
And then ask yourself,
要是他们炸掉的是你的那艘飞船呢
what if it were your ship they were blowing up?
你是乘火箭来地球的
You came here in a rocket.
像篮子里的小孩  像个摩西
Child in a basket, you know? Real Moses stuff.
现在给你一个机会  告诉这些领导人
Here's your chance to tell the bosses
放了你的同类人
to "Let your people go."
不然就让我们这些祸患来帮你
Or us plagues'll do it for ya.
总统先生
Mr. President.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
我不会为保护我的国家而道歉
I will not apologized for protecting my country.
我就在保护你的国家
But that's why you have me.
对奥利维亚·马斯丁来说  可能这就够了
That may have sufficed for Olivia Marsdin.
但现在不同
Not anymore.
所有和克莱莫有关的人
Everyone involved in Claymore,
所有在卫星基地工作的人
everyone that works at that satellite base
都有危险
is at risk.
精英要发动袭击了
The Elite are going to attack.
如果我关闭了
If I closed every military base
所有可能受威胁的军事基地  就一个不剩了
that might be threatened, I'd have no bases left.
而且提醒你一下  我不需要对你负责
And last I checked, I don't answer to you.
那等到克莱莫
Will you answer to your electorate
击落第一架没有恶意的外星飞船
the first time Claymore shoots down an alien ship
你要对你的选民负责吗
that means us no harm?
这样是错的  会有无辜的人死亡
It's wrong. Innocent people will die.
你不要插手卫星的事
Do not interfere with that satellite!
这是个错误  总统先生
This is a mistake, Mr. President.
转到187号扰码
Go to scrambler code 1-8-7.
将军  把克莱莫提前到明天晚上发射
General, move the Claymore launch up to tomorrow night.
加强恶魔塔的警戒
And double the guard at Devil's Tower.
没事  只是拍个照
It was fine. It was a photo op.
我着好装然后...
I wore the suit and...
好吧  好像有点过了
Yeah, that probably was a little bit much.
酒店里有个人  他...
There was this guy at the hotel who, uh...
没关系  莉迪娅
Doesn't matter, Lydia. Um...
你知道吗  宝贝  我...
You know what, sweetheart? I--
我一直能听见爸爸的声音
I just keep hearing Dad's voice
在我脑海里
in my head,
说我跟那些政客打交道
and he's telling me that I'm an idiot
这种行为非常愚蠢
for rubbing elbows with all these politicians
因为我建立自由之子
when I started the Children of Liberty
本是为了帮助人
to help people.
真正的人类
Real people.
我还坚持初心吗  还是
Am I still doing that? Or, um...
不说这个了  你还好吗
Anyway, uh, how are you doing?
乔治呢  我想跟你谈谈...
How's George? I wanted to talk to you--
您的留言时长已用尽
Your message has reached its limit.
来吧
Come on.
不  不要
No. No.
不不不
No. No. No. No.
星体投射失败
Bad astral projection.
你背着我偷来这里
You went behind my back.
你利用了那个白痴凯里克斯
You took advantage of that simpleton Kelex.
然后开始星体投射了
And now you're astral projecting.
你跳过了中间好几个月的训练
That jumps months of training.
我知道  抱歉  我只是...
I know, I'm sorry. I just...
我太着急行动了  我就是急性子
I move too fast 'cause that's what I do.
我给自己施压  去承担扛不住的压力
I push myself and I take on more than I can handle.
我妈总是这样说
My mother always said it.
但是英雄就该这么做
But that's what heroes do.
身先士卒
Leaping before one looks
是英雄的本能
is part of the job description.
-它适得其反了  -是
- It backfired. - Yes.
但是下次  你要勇往直前
But next time, you shall fire forward.
我不知道你还上门服务
I didn't know you made house calls.
你的家真好
Your place is great.
我来这里是为了克莱莫行动
I'm here about Operation Claymore.
总统正计划发射卫星
The President is planning on launching a satellite array
炸毁任何进入地球轨道的
that will blow up any alien spacecraft
外星飞船
entering our orbit.
什么  超查部才应该是抵抗外星入侵的
What? The DEO's supposed to be the first line of defense
第一防线  不是什么巨炮
against invasions. I mean, not some giant gun.
-这样合法吗  -我不知道
- Is that even legal? - I don't know.
但我知道这样做不道德
But I do know it's immoral.
但是我所做的一切对人们都有影响
But everything I do means something to people,
所以
so...
如果我阻止了卫星发射
If I stop the satellite,
我便与精英为伍
I'm aligning myself with the Elite.
但如果不阻止  让卫星发射
And then on the other hand, if I let the launch happen,
这又顺应了自由之子的理念
what does that say to the Children of Liberty?
为什么我觉得进退两难
Why does it feel like there are only two choices?
你不是有着自己的理念吗
And aren't you on your own side?
是的
Yes.
孤独一人
Alone.
-有时这就像是  -朝着虚空呐喊  不会有回应
- Sometimes it feels like-- - Screaming into the void.
我妹妹说过这句话
That's something my sister said.
听着
Look,
你应该做自己觉得对的事情
you can only do what you feel is right.
是的
Yeah.
跟我走
Come with me.
和海军陆战队谈谈
Talk to the Marine Corps.
你是超查部的局长
You're the Director of the DEO,
卖弄一下你的权势
throw your weight around.
如果我出现  那会危及我的职位
If I show up, I would jeopardize my position
整个组织都会岌岌可危
and the whole organization would be at risk.
我不能这么做
I can't.
我理解
I understand.
我想说也许在监狱里染发
I'm just saying maybe a prison dye job
不是最好的选择
wasn't the best move.
出老千也不是  伙计
Nor is base dealing, mate.
差一张老K
Needed a third king.
-杜松子酒  -以为你不会问呢
- Gin. - Thought you'd never ask.
什么事  姑娘
What's that, girl?
在老磨坊遇到了麻烦
Trouble at the old mill?
没错
Right.
你猜对了
You called it.
钢铁女侠直接去找总统了
Girl of Steel went straight to the President.
那个傻瓜将发射时间提前至明天
Idiot moved the launch up to tomorrow.
发射基地位于怀俄明州
Base is in Wyoming.
恶魔塔
Devil's Tower.
怀俄明州  恶魔塔
你怎么知道我们要来
How did you know we were comin'?
当然是有跟踪装置了
Fish and chips and tracking devices.
一切都结束了
This ends now.
你还是寡不敌众
You're still outnumbered.
再数数
Count again.
这是谁
Who's this, then?
你有精英团队
You have the Elite...
我有超级伙伴
I have super friends.
好的
Right.
糟糕
Oh, crap!
我来帮你们
I got you.
去找那个火星人
Go after the Martian.
厉害了
Rad.
厉害
我制造了手套用来集中原始梦境能量
I built the gloves to harness raw dream energy!
所以  没错  是很"厉害"
So, yes, it's quite "Rad."
你们安全了  赶快出去
You're safe now. Get out of here.
来呀
Go on.
转过头来
Turn the other cheek.
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers?
我做了我认为对的事
I did what I thought was right.
-荣恩  -卫星
- J'onn... - The satellite.
没错
Right.
-你怎么知道我要在哪  -梦境
- How'd you know where I-- - Dreams.
微分推算
Differential calculus.
我的戒指去哪了
Where's my ring?
敏捷的手法  像我一样  你知道吗
Sleight of hand, fam. Like me. You see...
这只是调虎离山罢了
I'm just a distraction.
等等
Wait...
莫拉人去哪里了
Where's the Morae?
布莱尼  他们启动了卫星发射
Brainy, they started the launch.
控制中心被毁  我也束手无策
The controls are destroyed. I can't do anything.
我的计划实现了  不是吗
Well, that was the plan, wasn't it?
准备发射
Launch initiated.
-你做了什么  -我自己选定了目标
- What did you do? - Picked my own target.
宾州大道1600号  白宫
1600 Penn. The White House.
你的政府将被自己制造的炮火炸毁
Your government, on fire, hoisted by its own petard.
一旦它到达地球轨道  就会开火
As soon as it reaches orbit, it will fire.
它被称作"扮演上帝"是有原因的
There's a reason it's called "Playing God."
真有趣
It's fun.
飞吧
Fly.
想让我成为地球上最幸福的人吗
Wanna make me the happiest man on Earth?
你来了呀  荣恩·荣兹
There you are, J'onn J'onzz.
很高兴最终见到你了
Nice to finally meet you.
我知道你为什么找我
I know why you called me, now.
你想死
You have a death wish.
卫星抵达地球轨道
Satellite has reached orbit.
倒数开火  七  六  五
Firing in seven, six, five,
四  三  二
four, three, two,
一
one.
你还好吗
You okay?
那枚戒指
That ring...
是我的
was mine.
被我弄丢了
And I lost it.
听着
Look,
如果你过去几天教会了我任何事
if you've taught me anything the past couple of days,
那就是挫折让你更加强大
it's that setbacks will make you stronger.
这和戒指被偷没有关系  布莱尼
It's not about how your ring was stolen, Brainy.
我们要想着怎么把戒指拿回来
It's about how we're gonna get it back.
谢谢你  尼娅·纳尔
Thank you, Nia Nal.
你的头怎么样
How's your head?
别担心
Don't worry about it.
别告诉总统就行
Just don't tell the President.
你没来过这里
You were never here.
你做了件好事  摧毁卫星
You did a good thing, destroying that satellite.
没有那件战服我是无法做到的
Well, I couldn't have done it without that suit.
但精英仍逍遥法外
But the Elite are still out there.
我们会抓到他们的
Oh, we'll get 'em.
听着
Look...
官方来说  我知道我们不该交流
Officially, I know that we're not really supposed to communicate.
我不是说你随便什么时候都能来
And I'm not saying that you can just show up whenever you want.
但是  你懂的  偶尔几次
But, you know, occasionally, from time to time,
-或许我们可以  -就像我们以前那样
- maybe, uh, we can-- - Kick ass the way we used to?
差不多吧
Something like that.
我非常愿意
I would really like that.
祝我好运吧
Well, uh, wish me luck.
我要找个人谈谈卫星的事
I gotta go see a guy about a satellite.
祝你好运
Good luck.
发射这个卫星是为了保护美国人
That satellite array was created to protect Americans.
更别提那东西花了20亿美元
Not to mention that it cost $2 billion!
卫星毁了  我们落得如此下场
And now it's gone. And here we are.
但我们还活着
Yes, here we are.
还有你的员工  你所爱之人
As well as your staff, your loved ones...
幸亏我没有
Thanks to me wasn't leveled
被政府创造的武器击落
by a weapon of its own government's creation.
得了吧你  你告诉我
Come on, you can tell me.
你讨厌那颗卫星
You hated that satellite.
你是个超级英雄
You're a superhero.
肯定有办法在不炸掉卫星的情况下
There had to have been a way to stop Claymore
阻止克莱莫
without blowin' it up.
不  你炸掉它是因为你想这么做
No, you did it because you wanted to.
我向你保证  长官  别无他法
I assure you, sir, there was no other way.
上校  我能和你谈谈吗
Colonel, a word?
现在不是时候
It's not a good time.
下次政府要开展
The next time the government institutes
一个秘密的外星人防御计划时
a secret extraterrestrial defense program,
我非常感谢能参与其中
I would appreciate being part of the conversation.
克莱莫行动应属于超查部的职权范围
Operation Claymore should have been DEO purview.
如果我不了解国家安全事务
If I'm not briefed on matters of national security,
-就无法做好我的工作  -等一下
- then I can't do my job. - Just a moment.
我不知道
I didn't know.
什么
Sorry?
总统没有按规章行事
President acted against protocol.
我毫不知情
I was never informed.
因此  那导致了2%的增长
So, that results in a 2% increase in--
-我的天  -老天
- Oh, my God! - Jeez.
怎么了
Um, what happened?
没什么
Oh, it... It's fine.
我觉得你是对的
I think you're right.
这个政府有问题
There's something wrong with this government.
我以为你就是政府的人
I thought you were the government.
不  我是你的朋友
No, I'm your friend.
现在  我对你非常有信心
And right now I have a hell of a lot more faith in you
而不是他们
than I do in them.
不管你需要什么  随你差遣
So, whatever you need, I'm here.
很好
Good.
我相信你
That I can trust.
明天再来  我们带你好好地参观
Come back tomorrow, we'll give you the real tour.
本
Ben!
很高兴你愿意再来
I'm glad you made the second trip.
非常感谢
I really appreciate it.
当然  总统先生
Of course, Mr. President.
今天发生了很多事情  很多不和
Lotta things going on today. Lotta moving parts.
我相信也是  长官
Hmm, I can believe it, sir.
那是当然
Of course, you do.
信仰  忠诚  才是重要的
Belief, loyalty. It's important, hmm?
不是针对穿披风的某人
Maybe not to certain caped individuals.
我一直在思考  本
See, I've been thinking, Ben...
我或许没办法给所有的自由之子赋予职权
I may not be able to deputize all of your Children of Liberty,
但是我可以赋职一个
but I can deputize one.
你愿意做
How would you like to be
我的下一任外星事务部部长吗
my next Director of Alien Affairs?
什么
What?
我们需要你这样的人
We could use a man like you.
一个有自知之明的人
A man who knows what he is.
本·洛克伍德被任命为外星事务部部长
"本届政府的宝贵财富"
"An asset to this administration."
难以置信
It's unbelievable.
这段时间总统做了
Yeah, the President is making some
一些非常奇怪的决定
very strange decisions lately.
洛克伍德的任命  卫星
The Lockwood appointment, satellite...
-你怎么  -布莱尼告诉我的
- How do you-- - Brainy told me.
-我们一起吃的早午餐  -真棒
- We get brunch. - Cute.
-是的  -没错
- Yeah. - Yeah.
在这个问题上  我有很多想法
My instincts were all over the place on this one.
不知道该选择哪个
Didn't know which way was up.
现在还也不清楚
Still not sure if I do.
我知道那种感觉
Yeah, I know the feeling.
我有个报道  不知道该不该由我来跟进
I got this story I'm not sure if I should pursue myself.
你怎么弄清楚的
How'd you figure it out?
检查我的动机
Examined my motives.
确定我做出的决定
Made sure the decision I was making
是有着正确的原因
was for the right reasons
而非出于自私
and not the selfish ones.
我想那就是我们真正能做的  对吗
I guess that's all we can do really, right?
对
Yeah.
说到这里
Speaking of which,
我有另一篇报道要写
I've got another article to write.
写快点
Type fast.
超快
Super speed.
麦肯齐
Mackenzie.
你之前提到的线人
That source that you were mentioning,
你认为他会愿意公开发言吗
do you think that he'd be willing to speak on the record?
你们都和我一样看见相同之景
You all saw the exact same thing I did.
我们需要地面部队
We need boots on the ground,
-而不是站在讲台上的衣着光鲜的  -先生们
- not wingtips on a dais-- - Gentlemen.
抱歉  我才想起来我们要见面
Sorry, I didn't realize that we were meeting until--
我的错
My fault.
一定是忘记了
Must've forgot.
这些都是一直坚守阵地的人
These here are all the folks that've been holding the fort down in...
来看看  东北部的
Well, let's see. Nor'east,
卡罗莱纳州  海湾地区  新墨西哥州
Carolinas, Gulf, New Mexico.
这位是本·洛克伍德
This is Ben Lockwood.
对不起  是洛克伍德部长吗
I'm sorry, is it... Is it Director Lockwood?
这看起来很像我的面具  库珀
This kinda looks a lot like, uh, my mask, Coop.
我们都是自由代表
Well, we're all Agent Liberty.
就像你说的  对吧
It's like you said, isn't it?
不管我们是谁
Doesn't matter who we are.
不管领导者是谁
Doesn't matter who leads.
当然
Sure, um--
或许有其他看法
Except I think it might.
"代表"是行动的代表
"Agent" means you act.
我们都感觉你只在空谈
We're all feeling like you're all talk,
没有行动
no action.
自由之子需要一个可以激励他们的领导者
The Children of Liberty need a leader who inspires them.
一个强大的  有能力的
Someone strong and powerful--
还有人在考虑更换领导吗
Is anyone else entertaining a change in leadership?
没有
No?
那好
Good.
我们继续
Let's proceed.